The caterer sent me this list of 12 appetizers. I have to narrow it to 6.
外烩的公司给我十二道开胃菜清单 我得将选择范围缩小到六项
Food? Oh, give me.
食物问题？交给我吧
Did Monica mention we're trying to get The Swing Kings to play the wedding?
摩妮卡跟你们提过我们结婚时 要请摇摆国王来演唱吗？
You're into swing music?
你喜欢摇摆音乐？
I used to go all over town listening to bands.
我以前会跑遍全城听乐团演奏
-Chandler? -Gap commercial.
-钱德？ -在GAP的广告看到的
-Did you book them? Did you call? -I will.
-你打电话订下他们了吗？ -我会打的
-You want me to call? -I'll do it. You stick to your job.
-你要我打吗？ -我会打的，你只需要做好你的工作
-What is your job? -Staying out of the way.
-你的工作是什么？ -别碍事
This is impossible. Why don't you just pick all 15?
这是不可能的，你为什么不挑清单上的十五道开胃菜？
-There were only 12. -Oh, yeah, I added 3.
-只有十二道而已 -对，我加了三道
What are "peanut-butter fingers"?
什么是花生酱手指？
The One With the Cheap Wedding Dress
本集播出：廉价的婚纱
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Well, hello.
你好
She's cute.
她好可爱
Should we go talk to her?
我们该跟她说话吗？
Sure. Being engaged, I'm not nervous to talk to pretty girls anymore.
当然，订婚后跟美女说话 我再也不会紧张
Could you guys help me?
你们能过来帮帮我吗？
Yeah, let me get that for you.
我来帮你搬那个
-It's really heavy. -I got it.
-它真的很重 -没问题
So hi, I'm Ross, and this is my friend, Chandler.
嗨，我是罗斯，他是我朋友钱德
I'm Kristen.
我是克丽丝汀
Hi. Are you new to the area?
克丽丝汀，嗨，你刚搬来吗？
I'd love to show you around sometime.
如果你刚搬来这里 我可以带你四处参观一下
I actually just moved from four blocks over.
事实上，我从四条街外搬来这里
But this block is like another world.
但这里好像另一个世界
Actually, it does have a very interesting history.
事实上这个地区的历史非常有趣
This street is the first in the city to have an underground sewer system.
这条街是纽约 第一条有下水道系统的街道
Before that, sewage and waste...
之前污水跟废弃物…
would just flow right down the street.
会直接流到街上
Sometimes ankle-deep.
有时深及脚踝
Smooth.
说的好
Excuse me?
你说什么？
You're gonna be starving after moving. What do you say I take you to dinner?
搬完家后你一定会肚子饿 你想跟我一起去吃晚餐吗？
-I'd like that. -Great.
-我很乐意 -太棒了
Let me take this up.
我帮你把箱子搬上去
-After you. -Oh, no. After you.
-你先请 -不，你先请
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Am I crazy, or does this totally go?
是我疯了还是这真的很配？
Oh, my God! You look so beautiful!
我的天啊！你看起来好漂亮！
Thank you, Rachel. But look at Monica!
谢谢你，瑞秋，但看看摩妮卡！
This is it. Yeah, this is the one.
就是它，就是这件
I can't believe I found it.
我不敢相信我找到它了
Wow, you look so beautiful. If I knew you, I'd cry.
你看起来好漂亮 如果我认识你，我会哭的
I'm Monica Geller. Bawl like a baby.
我是摩妮卡盖勒，幸福的新娘
I'm Megan Bailey.
我是梅根巴利
-Have you found your dress? -These dresses are amazing...
-你找到婚纱了吗？ -这些婚纱都很漂亮…
-but I couldn't afford one. -I can't either.
-但我买不起 -我也是
I'm here to figure out the one I want,  then I'll get it at Kleinman's.
我只是来这里找婚纱 然后我会到克莱门婚纱店买
They're having a huge sale.
他们在大减价
-Thanks for the tip. -When are you getting married?
-谢谢你的情报 -你什么时候结婚？
-I'm not. I just like to try them on. -I do the same thing.
-我没有要结婚，我只是想试穿婚纱 -我也会那么做
I'm just kidding. I'm getting married July 25th.
我只是在开玩笑 我的婚期是七月二十五日
I'm just kidding too.
我也只是在开玩笑
I'm getting married in December.
我要在十二月结婚
-When are you getting married? -May 15th.
-你什么时候结婚？ -五月十五日
It's close. Who's your photographer?
已经很接近了，你请谁拍照？
-Jeffrey. -We met with him.
-杰佛瑞 -我们跟他谈过
-Did he show you nude wedding photos? -The Best Man? Wow!
-他拿裸体婚纱照给你们看了吗？ -那个伴郎吗？哇！
I know. I almost called off my wedding.
我知道，我差点取消了婚礼
-Who's your band? -My fiance wants The Swing Kings.
-你请了哪个乐团？ -我未婚夫想请摇摆国王
You're lucky. My fiance wants the heavy metal band, Carcass.
你真幸运，我未婚夫想请尸体 那重金属乐团
Is that spelled with a "C" or a "K"? It doesn't matter, they're both great!
是湿体还是尸体？ 那不重要，他们都很棒！
Oh, don't buy that here.
别在这里买婚纱
Now that you know what you want,  go to Kleinman's.
现在你知道你喜欢哪一件 到克莱门婚纱店买
This place is so overpriced.
这里的婚纱太贵了
I own this store.
我是这里的老板
So does this come in another color, or...
这件婚纱有别的颜色吗？还是…？
Hi. You moving in or moving out?
嗨，你要搬进来还是搬走？
-Moving in. -Can I help out?
-我要搬进来 -需要我帮忙吗？
Okay, but be careful. The guy who was helping before hurt his back.
好吧，但是你得小心一点 来帮我的那个人因为背痛先走了
-Boyfriend? -No.
-他是你男朋友？ -不是
I'm Joey.
我是乔伊
Kristen.
我是克丽丝汀
What a beautiful name.
你的名字真好听
What is it again?
你说你叫什么来着？
Kristen.
克丽丝汀
-You live around here? -Right down there.
-你住在附近？ -我就住在那边
Let me give you a tip.
我得提供你一些资讯
Don't take a nap on this stoop. You could wake up without shoes.
别在那个楼梯上睡觉 醒过来时你的鞋子可能已经被偷了
I'll remember that.
我会记住的
Listen, would you like to have dinner with me tonight?
听着，今晚你要跟我一起吃饭吗？
I have plans tonight. How about tomorrow?
今晚我有约了，明天可以吗？
Sounds great. Well, where does this go?
听起来不错，这个要搬到哪里？
You look strong. Why don't you grab one of the boxes.
你看起来很壮，把它交给我 你去帮我搬箱子吧
（书，枕头）
Yeah, I'll get this one.
对，我要挑这一个
（克莱门婚纱店五折大减价）
So this is Brooklyn?
这里就是布鲁克林？
Listen up. There's only one dress in each size.
听着，通常每件婚纱 一个尺寸只有一件
So when they open those doors,  fan out.
他们一开门，马上冲进去
This is what you're looking for. Memorize it.
这就是你们的目标，记住它
When you locate the dress,  blow on these, all right?
找到婚纱后就吹哨子，好吗？
Three sharp blasts. When you hear it, come running.
用力吹三声，一听到哨音后 马上跑过来
Here he comes!
他来了！
-They're pushing! -Don't be a baby!
-她们在推我！ -别那么孩子气！
-Out of the way! -Let's go!
-别挡路！ -我们冲吧！
Rachel?! Come on!
瑞秋？！快一点！
No, not it. Not it. Not it.
不，不是
Don't crowd me.
别推我
This is it! This is the dress! It's perfect!
就是它！就是这件婚纱！太完美了！
I'm sorry, this one's taken!
对不起，这件是我的！
-Megan! -Monica!
-梅根！ -摩妮卡！
-You came! -Yeah!
-你来了！ -对！
-This is my dress! -No!
-这是我的婚纱！ -不！
-You saw me wearing it. -And now you'll see me buying it.
-你看到我试穿它 -现在你会看到我买下它
You freak!
你这个怪胎！
You wouldn't even know about this place without me.
如果没有我你根本不知道这个地方
-Look, you don't want to fight me. -Maybe I do. I'm pretty feisty!
-听着，你不会想跟我争 -或许我想，我是很凶的！
-I'm coming! I'm coming! -Hey!
-我来了… -嘿！
Okay! Hey? Oh, what do I do?!
好了！嘿？我该怎么办？！
What are you doing? Did you find the dress?
你在做什么？你找到婚纱了吗？
Did you find the dress?
你找到婚纱了吗？
No. You gotta get me out of here.
不，快救我出去，这些女人都疯了
-We've gotta get Monica. -You hold my hand!
-我们得去找摩妮卡 -你得抓住我的手！
Excuse me! Excuse me!
对不起…
Go! Go! Go!
快走…
（中央公园咖啡厅）
How was your date the other night?
罗斯，那天你跟她约会还顺利吧？
Did you tell her about the magical ride that starts with every flush?
你跟她提过只要一按马桶 魔法之旅就开始了吗？
Laugh all you want, but she said she'd like to go out again.
尽管笑吧，但她说她想再跟我约会
In fact, I'll go call her right now.
事实上，我正要打电话给她
And I'll make sure and tell her my friend Chandler says...
我会确定并告诉她我朋友钱德说…
Sorry I didn't stop by last night, but I had a date.
抱歉昨晚我失约了，但我有个约会
When it's 1:00 in the morning and you don't come by, that's okay.
你说你凌晨一点要过来 就算你放我鸽子也没有关系
It was with this really hot girl who moved in across the street.
我跟一个辣妹约会，她刚刚搬到对街
-Right across the street? -Yeah.
-真的吗？她住在对街？ -对
-When did you meet her? -Two days ago.
-你什么时候认识她的？ -两天前
Excellent!
太棒了！
You know, Ross met somebody too.
罗斯也认识了一个女孩
-Hey. -How'd it go?
-嘿 -怎么样？
We're going out again Saturday.
太棒了，我们星期六要再出去玩
But I found out she's also seeing some other guy.
但我刚刚发现她也在跟别人约会
Really?
真的吗？
Joe, what would you do if you were in Ross' situation?
乔伊，如果你是罗斯你会怎么做？
I am. I'm dating this girl who's also seeing another guy.
我跟他差不多 跟我约会的女孩也在跟别人约会
But I'm not worried about it.
但我一点都不担心
You shouldn't be. I wouldn't want to be the guy who's up against you.
你不必担心，我不想当你的竞争者
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
那个混蛋一定会输的
So this is nice.
这真的太有趣了
I wish I didn't have to go. Believe me.
真希望我能留下来，相信我
But I have to.
但我得走了
So, what's the name of the girl you're dating?
对了，跟你们约会的女孩 叫什么名字？
-Kristen Leigh. -Bye.
-克丽丝汀莱夫 -再见
Well, only one of us can keep dating her.
很明显地，我们之中 只有一个人能继续跟她约会
Obviously. So how do we decide?
没错，我们该怎么决定？
Well, now,  let's look at this objectively.
好了，我们得客观地来解决这件事
I think I should date her.
我想我该跟她约会
Or I'm the one who dates her.
或是我该跟她约会
That's interesting. But check this out. I date her.
那真的很有趣 但是听好了，我跟她约会
Okay, but to go in another direction..
好吧，但是换个角度来说…
Okay. This can go on for a while.
好吧，我们是谈不出结论来的
-We should order some food then. -No, Joey.
-那么我们该点些吃的 -不，乔伊
Look, why don't we just let her decide, okay?
听着，我们为什么不让她来决定呢？
We'll each go out with her one more time.
我们都再跟她约会一次
And we'll see who she likes best.
看看她比较喜欢谁
That sounds fair.
听起来很公平
Maybe I'll take her to that new French restaurant.
或许我会带她 到新开的法国餐厅吃饭
Wait a second. We have to set a spending limit.
等一下，我们得对约会费用设下限制
I can't take her to a fancy place like that.
我没有钱带她到高级餐厅吃饭
Well, sorry. That's what I do on dates.
抱歉，那是我的约会方式
Well, I guess I'll just have to do what I do on dates.
我猜我得用我的约会方式
-So let's decide on a spending limit. -Yeah.
-我们来决定费用上限 -好吧
And a slice...
大概是…
six dollars?
六块钱？
-I was thinking more like 100. -Okay.
-我想是一百块 -好吧
Can I borrow 94 dollars?
你能借我九十四块吗？
I know. Can you hand me a tissue?
我知道，你能帮我拿张面纸吗？
You're out of Diet Coke.
你家没有健怡可乐了
Hello?
喂？
What? You what?
什么？你什么？
You listen here, missy!
你给我听好了，小姐！
Megan booked The Swing Kings on the day of our wedding...
是梅根打来的，她订下摇摆国王 日期是我们结婚的那一天…
and said she'd only give them back for the dress!
还说如果我不把婚纱让给她 我就没有乐团
Does that mean Carcass is available?
那么说的话尸体有空了？
What am I gonna do? That's the dress! That is "the" dress!
我该怎么办？我好喜欢那件婚纱！
Chandler wants the band. What do I do?
钱德喜欢那个乐团，我该怎么办？
-Figure out how to talk him out of it. -How?
-想办法说服他放弃 -怎么说服？
You're out of toilet paper!
你家的卫生纸用完了！
I wanted to wish you good luck on your date.
我要来祝你约会顺利
-Thanks. -What time are you meeting?
-谢谢 -你们约几点？
We have reservations at Grand Merci Bistro at 8.
我们在葛兰梅西毕斯多餐厅 订了八点的位子
That's in 20 minutes. You'd better get dressed.
时间只剩二十分钟 你最好快去换衣服
-I am dressed. -Oh, well, good.
-我已经换好衣服了 -太好了
For me.
对我来说
What's this? Did you give yourself a facial?
这是什么？你在敷脸？
I have an oily T-zone.
我的T字部位很会出油
Okay, dude.
好吧，兄弟
-You sent Kristen flowers? -That's right.
-你送克丽丝汀花？ -没错
You spent 100 dollars. That's the limit. You're screwed!
你花了一百块 你把钱花光了，你输了！
I sent the flowers before the actual date, so technically...
我在约会前送她花 所以技术上来说…
I didn't break any rules.
我没有犯规
Thanks for stopping by though.
谢谢你来看我
That's how it's gonna be? I can break the rules too.
你真的要那么玩？我也可以犯规
-What are you gonna do? -I don't know.
-你打算怎么办？ -我不知道
-I'm not surprised. -You won't get away with this.
-为什么我一点都不讶异？ -我不会放过你的
-You don't have much choice. -We'll see!
-我想你没有太多选择 -我们走着瞧
Hey! So, just a light layer?
嘿！只要薄薄地敷一层就好？
Yeah, just here and there.
对，只要敷这里跟这里
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
乔伊又把肉酱滴在栏杆上了
Swing music is so out.
摇摆音乐太落伍了
He's gotta be in the room for that to work.
他得在这房间里才可以听的到
What are you guys talking about?
你们到底在说什么？
We're talking about The Swing Kings...
我们在谈摇摆国王…
and whether they're the right way to go.
讨论到底该不该请他们来
I went to a wedding where they had swing music...
有一次我去参加 请摇摆乐团来表演的婚礼…
two months later the couple divorced.
两个月后他们就离婚了
I'm not saying there's any connection here...
我不是说这其中有什么关系…
but they did say that's why they got divorced.
但他们的确告诉我 那是他们离婚的原因
But I love swing music!
但我喜欢摇摆音乐！
But The Swing Kings?
但摇摆国王？
They suck so much that people die at their concerts. They stop living.
他们烂到有人听他们的演唱会死掉 他们就是不想活了
When Monica and I went to see them,  we had fun.
我只知道摩妮卡跟我 去看他们演唱时非常开心
And there's another reason.
事实上还有一个原因
-Well, what is the other reason? -I don't want to say.
-是什么原因？ -我不想说
Well, you have to,  because maybe it's stupid.
你非说不可，或许它很愚蠢
It's just, while Monica and I were dancing to them...
摩妮卡跟我随着他们的音乐起舞…
it was the first time I knew that...
我第一次知道…
you were the woman that I wanted to dance all my dances with.
你就是我想一辈子共舞的女人
Oh, crap.
喔，烂透了
-Our table will be ready soon. -Oh, great.
-我们的桌子马上就会准备好 -太棒了
-Is your back feeling better? -That's fine.
-你的背好一点了吗？ -没事了
I guess the more muscles you have...
我猜肌肉越多…
the more they can spasm out of control.
就越可能抽筋
-Kristen? -Joey!
-克丽丝汀？ -乔伊！
-What are you doing here? -I like this place.
-你来这里做什么？ -我喜欢这个地方
And technically, I'm not breaking any rules, so...
技术上来说，我没有犯规，所以…
Well, Ross, this is Joey. Joey, Ross.
罗斯，他是乔伊 乔伊，罗斯
-Hi. -Hi. It's nice to meet you.
-嗨 -嗨，很高兴能认识你
I used to have a friend named Joey.
我以前有个朋友叫乔伊
I don't anymore.
但他不再是我朋友
Our table will be ready in a couple minutes.
我们的桌子马上就会准备好
Sure! I would love to wait with you guys! Thanks!
当然，我想跟你们一起等！谢谢！
So, Joey, you look familiar.
乔伊，你看起来好眼熟
Are you on TV or something?
你上过电视吗？
He doesn't like to talk about it...
乔伊不喜欢提这件事…
but he's one of the stars of Days of Our Lives.
但他主演过《我们的日子》
That's right. Don't you play a woman?
没错，你不是演女人吗？
A woman in a man's body.
那是被困在男人身体里的女人
Much better.
那可好多了
It's funny, because you look familiar to me too.
真有趣，因为我也觉得你很眼熟
Have you ever been married?
你结过婚吗？
Yes, I have.
我结过婚
In fact, just the other day...
事实上，前几天…
Kris and I talked about how I've been married and have a son.
克丽丝跟我还谈到 我结过婚，有个儿子
-Little Eric. -That's right. Wait. No, Ben.
-小艾力克 -没错，等一下，不，是班才对
So you've just been married the one time then?
你只结过一次婚吗？
-Well... -You've been married twice?
-嗯… -你结过两次婚？
Yes. And...
对，那个…
another time after that.
之后又结了一次
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
天啊，我饿了
Have you ever been so hungry on a date...
你曾经在约会时饿到…
that when the girl goes to the bathroom, you eat her food?
趁女伴去上洗手间 偷吃掉她的食物吗？
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
你说服务生吃掉我的蟹饼
So, Ross, now why did that first marriage break up?
罗斯，你的第一段婚姻为什么会结束？
Was it because the woman was straight or because she was a lesbian?
因为你前妻是异性恋 或因为她是同性恋？
-Do you two know each other? -No.
-你们认识吗？ -不认识
But he seems like a guy who'd marry a woman...
只是罗斯看起来像是 会跟有同性恋倾向的女人…
on the verge of being a lesbian and then push her over the edge.
结婚后，逼得她非得出柜的男人
Wait a minute! Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
等一下，你拍过淋病海报吧？
Have you ever slept in the same bed with a monkey?
你跟猴子同床共枕过吧？
You leave Marcel out of this!
别把马赛扯进来！
Fine! You ever gotten stuck in a pair of leather pants?
好吧，你曾经被自己的皮裤卡住了？
Have you ever locked yourself in a TV cabinet, VD-boy?
你曾经把自己锁在电视柜里吗？电视小子
Monkey-lover!
猴子迷！
Where do you think we lost her?
你觉得她是什么时候离开的？
Probably around gonorrhea.
可能是淋病那一段吧
-Hi, honey, I'm home! -Don't come in here!
-甜心，我回来了！ -别进来！
Why, do you have another boyfriend in there?
怎么了？你的另一个男朋友在里面？
No. We only mess around at his place.
不，我们只会在他家胡搞
I started it, but now it's scaring me,  so could you come out here?
虽然是我开的头 但我开始担心了，你能出来吗？
I'm wearing a wedding dress.
不行，我正穿着婚纱
You got a wedding dress?
你买到婚纱了？
-Yeah, but I'm not keeping it. -Then why can't I see it?
-对，但我要把它退回去 -那么我为什么不能看到它？
Oh. I guess you can.
我猜应该可以
But I have to return it, so you can't like it.
但我得把它退回去 所以你绝不能喜欢它
Okay, I promise. I'll hate it.
好吧，我发誓我会恨它
Wow. You look hideous.
哇，你看起来好可怕
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah. That's like the most ugliest dress I've ever seen.
对，那是我看过最丑的婚纱
Why do you have to return it?
你为什么要把它退回去？
Because it doesn't really fit.
因为它真的不合适
Oh, I booked The Swing Kings.
还有，我订了摇摆国王
Oh, that's great. Thanks.
那真的是太棒了，谢谢
But that dress is terrible.
但那件婚纱可怕极了
-It makes me want to rip it off you. -Okay.
-它让我想把它从你身上扯下来 -好吧
But you can't rip it.
但你不可以把它弄破
Well, maybe a little.
或许弄破一点也没关系
Guys, you want to look at the song list for the wedding?
你们想看看婚礼上 演唱歌曲的清单吗？
Guys?
怎么了？
I thought you'd be gone all day.
我还以为你会去一整天
All right, what's going on?
好吧，发生了什么事？
I'm sorry. I should probably leave you girls alone.
对不起，或许我应该 让你们这些小女生独处一下
Laugh all you want, but in 10 minutes we'll have younger-looking skin.
尽管笑吧，但十分钟后 我们的皮夫会变得又白又嫩
You know, she could use a little...
她该敷一下脸的…
Oh, nice shot! Yeah!
好球！太帅了！